Guide to the George Mason University photograph collection, 1950s-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 9: Creative Services, 1964-2007; (80 boxes)
  - Subseries 2: Chronological, 1981-2007
    - 1984, January 3-March 8, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      Unidentified people (headshots and in groups), copywork; Debate team / GMI meeting; GMI donation, King, art donation; John Allen, public affairs staff, Sarah Looney, Mathy House; nurses, snow scenes, Bowen, Levy; Tony Hickey, art donation, moving offices and library; Richmond, VA legislature; President George Johnson; Elly Doyle, Admissions counselors; Sociology, computer setup, President George Johnson at Faculty Senate; Arthur Peterson in class; Arthur Peterson (home), High-tech announcement press conference; President George Johnson at desk; Betsy Dahlin, Freer and Sackler Museum (?); dance class; Mary Berry, happy feet; satellite dish, Alex Haley; Counseling Center; Dan Rothbart, Fenwick Library, Murray Black with group; Faculty Senate meeting; Publications setup; copy work, circuit boards; Liu and Burke, Roth, Cozzins, Caulder; John Allen; International students; GMU authors, medal; Anita Taylor, David Bushnell, Brant Heatherington; Sheila Ffoliet, Joseph Simecca, Fenwick portrait
    - 1984, March 8-April 10, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Jan Cohen, copy work; Circuit boards; Kodalith copies; Carl Ernst, ice on trees; Martha Turnage; H. Feinstein, Fenwick Library, campus; Barocas and Hadad, Dale Foster; P.R. staff, archive material; Special Collections staff, Jim Fletcher, Byron Peters, computer; Faculty Senate officers, Bill Lankford, campus; Sarah Seeberg / Public Affairs staff, Claudia Murphy; D and P staph / Tri-x standards; Wiring campus, computer lab, general campus; Student forum; Campus, foreign nursing students; Palmieri and Cassara, Shannon Jordan, Fenwick Library; PAGE lounge, student publications editors and assistants; Shannon Jordan, Jose Bufil, Faculty and staff service awards; University Day, PAGE faculty, campus; President George Johnson, secretaries
    - 1984, April 13-July 23, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      Johnson Mobil donation, campus scenes; Minority students, campus; Law School library, Steve Burnett; Bill Lankford with slide projector; Mason Day; Pediatric nursing; Secretary's lunch, Nursing student; Counseling Center, Gary Axelson; David Brickley, Edgar Sibley; Student awards, Diane Miller; Dick Bausch; John McCarty; Market Process reception; Suzanne Dowdy, PhD graduates; Jo Pacheco, Betsy Dahlin with Joe D'Agostino; graduation; water sampling biology fieldtrip; Bill Cohn, Chris Thaiss; Taiwanese Art show / Aiko Miller reception; students, Aileen Furgeson, Bob Clark; GMI public choice luncheon, Rita Carty, Mr. and Mrs. Lampe with J. Broyhill; J. D'Agostino, campus, Arena construction; STP orientation; Dave Shaefer and assistant, Alan Screbnick; Fenwick Library; Brian Turner; Telecommunications staff, STP students; Evelyn Moore, Andy Evans; Westgate fellowship, ASSN scholarship; Minority student registration, Arena contract signing; Alumni move; Korean Deans with King; David Arrow; lighting test Joe O'Hara; Barry Render, Marion Deshmukh, Stephen Saperstone; Jane Flinn, Peter Black, Jon English
    - 1984, July 25-September 27, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; campus scenes; Computer classroom; construction; Charlene Hurt, Fenwick Library, Mrs. Johnson; Patriot's Day (?); Biology boat field trip; President George Johnson
    - 1984, October 2-December 12, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Arts Gala quilt, Patriot's Center construction; Biology boat field trip; students using computers; dance performance, Special Collections African artifacts; Weight lifting; President George Johnson; copy work; art exhibit; choral performance; Glenn Smith
    - 1985, January 9-March 15, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Volleyball; Art students; students at computers; snow scenes on campus; inside the National Gallery of Art; Cablecast facilities; dance class; theatre production; science labs; weight lifting; professors and students in classrooms; unidentified sculptor with rock
    - 1985, March 20-May 16, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Micheal Behramn, Robert Smith, John Allen, Ave Tombs; Kitty Smith, Fred Grossberg; Dance class and performance; sculptor at work; Cablecast facilities; volleyball; campus scenes; campus at night; Prasenjit Duara, Suzanne Slaydon, Carol Mattusch, John D'Amico, Stephen Goodwin; Track and field; Patriot Center; Jim Pfieffner, Ernest Cassara, Louis Golumb, James Laurey, John Radner; Marie Worzecka; Peter Kimmell, Jack Censer; Tina Greco being awarded ribbon by Vernon Dean (Washington Redskins), Chuckie Eldridge, Fairhill Center; Andy Soll
    - 1985, May 16-August 7, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Graduation; Sculpture with stone; Track and field; Archaeology Science & Technology; Fenwick library; groundskeepers working; Ron Shayka (Volleyball coach), information services, Don Marsh; student tour to Egypt; Frank Matthews, High tech, Leonard Liggio; Douglas Mose (Geology); Girard Mulherin; Stephen Saperstone (Math); Vernon Gras (English, GMU Press); Debra B. Bergoffen; Charles Friend (Law School), Margaret Brinig (Law School); Ben Cradall; Joseph Scimecca (Sociology and Anthropology); John Hooner (Central Receiving); Devon Hodges (English), Jack Censer (History); Martha Francescato; Anita Taylor (Communications); Marriott staff; Louis Meites (Chemistry); President George Johnson; Bruce B. Manchester, Sheryl Friedley
    - 1985, August 9-September 19, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events, copywork; Mrs. Johnson and vintage car; Paula Lewis; Marion Deshmukh (History), Arnald Gabriel (Performing Arts); Brack Brown (Public Affairs); Christopher Thaiss (PAGE, English); Bob Ehrlich (Physics); Jim Fonseca, Glenn Smith; Cynthia Lont, Benjamin Broome (Communication); Alice Andrews (Public Affairs); Melvin Friedlander (Public Affairs); Louis Meites; campus scenes, construction; pool hall, Fenwick Library; John Rishead (Psychology); Arena (Patriot Center); Jack Leye (Education); Hemlock Overlook; visiting artist music performance
    - 1985, September 20-October 11, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Mason Day (?); professors in classrooms and offices; theatrical performance; Arlington library; President George Johnson at desk; transportation leadership workshop; basketball at Patriot Center; Mail Room; Deana BaFundo, Director Summer Session, Joan Riemba, James Buie; John Socher (History), Charles K. Rowley (Center for study of Public Choice); Kenneth Boulding (visiting professor), John Seder (History); Center for study of Market Processes, Don Boudreaux, Jack High; George Selgin, Dan Levoie; Board of Visitors, Martha Penning, Brian Butch; Peter Brunette (English); David Kuebrich (English); J. Wade Gilley (Vice President); Jay Shapiro (Mathematics), France Pruitt; Young Chen Ru; William Lankford (Physics), Rei Berron (Foreign Languages and Literature), Jay Shapiro (Math)
    - 1985, October 11-26, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Patriot Center events; Bullets game at Patriot Center; Harold Gartner (Public Affairs), William James Haynie (Education); Sue Fitzgerald (Purchasing); Louis Guzman (Geography); Dennis Sandale, George Walker; Charles Russell (Law School); David Keever; Marjorie Brown-Azerowicz (Education); President George Johnson, A.G.M. Crawford; Joseph D. Gittler; Nick Ward (Art); Mary Sayer Hammend (Art); Jerry Clapsaddle (Art); Walter Kravitz (Art); Lois Harten (Sociology and Anthropology); Vicki Rader, Anthony Hickey; Stephen Diner (History); Ronald Jensen (History)
    - 1985, October 26-December 9, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Music performace; Dance performance; Eda Valero-Figueira; John Spaldo, Danusia Meson; Frank Matthews, John Burton; Miriam S. Raskin; Judith Hill, Frank Matthews; Mike McDermott; Maurice Sherrens, Miriam Raskin; Charles Vail; Basketball; President George Johnson playing golf, at home, with dog; Ruth Kaplan (Biology); Otto Wahl (Psychology); Jay Shapiro; John Bonfadini; Dance class; Prescription medications; Arts Gala; Housekeeping services; campus scenes; Nursing school, Fenwick Library; Nobuko Tsukui (English); Shep Krech, Carol Ondeck; Thomas Dietz; Barbara Knight; Rebecca Berbert; Faculty Art show, Inter-Club Council meeing
    - 1985-1986, December 9, 1985-April 15, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Harris Theatre orchestra event; Glenn Smith; Dance class; Ralph Roberts (Counseling Center), Lori Tiller; Jeremy Plant (Public Affairs); Deborah Kaplan (English), Roy Rosenzweig (History); Student theatre production; Stage hand protestors at Patriot Center; Volleyball; Carol Sears, Peter Defur; Transportation committee, Ellamae Doyle, Jayne Hart (Biology); Campus scenes; Nikki Giovanni; Exercise class; Steven Early, Robert Ehrlich, Eric Molin, Fred Siff; Louise White, Douglas Mose; Josephine Pacheco, Jan Cohn, Linda Seligman, Carl Ernst, Terry Comito; Manuel Johnson at the Treasury in D.C.; Posed student groups; Computer, Martin DeVys; Frank Petrene, Hans Bergman; Center for Middle East studies; Credit Union, Joe Showers, Abdi Bile; John O'Connor; Charlene Hurt in Fenwick Library, ballet shoes; Alexander Christakis; Fenwick Library; Construction, art exhibition
    - 1986, April 17-August 27, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Beatles look alike band; Art classroom; weight lifting, CPR training; Campus scenes; Cablecast facilities; graduation; Federal Theatre Project marionnettes; President George Johnson with students; Patriot Center; Hemlock Overlook; building construction; staff picnic; Til Hazel and Mrs. Johnson
    - 1986, August 28-November 19, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; campus scenes; Susan Shreve; weight lifting; Patriot's Day; Glenn Smith; Cablecast facilities; buildings on campus, aerial view of Patriot Center; basketball practice; basketball game
      contact sheets, photocopies
    - 1986-1987, November 19, 1986-February 20, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Wrestling, basketball; trap and skeet shooting; Adeed Dawisha on TV, indoor soccer; track and field; Walter Beam; Physical therapy; robot testing; buildings on campus; crew; ice and snow on campus; Humanities center drawings; Mrs. Johnson; Steven Kling, Keith Davies, President, Argentine Universities lunch, Nancy Bagrunoff, H.C. Quitmeyer; copy work; University Police; Mary Dzama, Blanche Skar; art exhibition
    - 1987, February 24-May 4, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Buildings on campus; Route 66 traffic; Campus scenes; Fenwick Library; "I study" license plate; exercise class; Ernest Boger; dance performance; Beverly Brown, Kelly Hawkins, John Hanks, George Mushrush; Computer lab
    - 1987, May 6-July 31, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; campus scenes; Alumni awards banquet; graduation; Don Boileau, Joe Gurfine; Til Hazel; Mrs. Johnson quilt making; Linda Dorough; Ann Tricilo (alumni); campus office moves; Law School
    - 1987, August 4-October 1, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Patriot Center; GMU bumber sticker; registration; campus scenes; Soccer; Institutional analysis OAIS; Track and field; Science labs; President George Johnson at Arlington; Cablecast facilities; CPR training; satellite dish; tennis; Mason Day (?)
      contact sheets, negatives
    - 1987, October 5-November 24, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      Unidentified people, meetings, events; Sandy Stinghl; Rugby; Campus scenes; Satellite dish; Slide library and professors; Conflict analysis; Rubenstein; Ellen Todd; dance group performing on campus, rowing machines; GMU sign and traffic; copy work; D'Andrea; sculpture, baby using computer; barn; soccer; Fairfax fire department; check presentation from Centennial Development corporation, Jim McGrath, Charles Baskerville; M. McDermott in "new office", Registrar's office setting up; Residence Halls III construction; "November is keep George Mason clean month"; copy work of U.S. Constitution; Ken Bumgardner with Jay Dietrich (Resident Student association), Freida Hartman; Arts Gala (?); Michael DiSalvo (Registrar); Dave Rossell, Paul Kashmer, John Sealock, Donna Schoonover; Marie O'Donnell, Douglas First, John Cobbs, Audrey Reynolds, Carol Lambiase, Doris Lavoie, Mary Boyle, Carmen Johnson; Felicia Johnson; campus construction
    - 1987-1988, December 2, 1987-January 29, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      Eileen Hogan, Keith Robbins, Library and Art Gallery; Charles White, Barbara Smith, Lorraine Brown, WPA books, Ruth Kerns, Rosemary; Parish Freeman, Luis Cardona, Tom MeScience & Technology, June Hull, Mary Clampet, Atoosa Resa, sculpture; Art students; R. Barnes (basketball practice), Stefanski in Artificial Intelligence lab, Glenn Smith new office; Douglas Mose with Radon kits, Music faculty moving into new offices; Millspaugh, Levine, Thompson, copies of Fuentes, Art Center, Artificial intelligence book; D. Oakley, C. Kormis, R. Barnes at GMU vs. William and Mary game, cheerleaders; Ryszard Michalski in office and Artificial Intelligence lab, Communications tower construction; Jesse Jackson, Rick Barnes, Carlos Fuentes, student (negatives scratched); Donald Mash, Fenwick Library and Robinson, copy work
    - 1988, February 2-23, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      Scott Derrick, Sue Shearouse, SUB II crew, Bookstore, shipping and receiving staff; C. Fuentes, D. Bergoffen, M. Baker, SUB II managers and staff; Wade Gilley, Anna Kondratas, Lee Cook, New York City Guide (WPA); Rick Barnes in basketball practice and game situations; Jesse Jackson in SUB II, Maureen Bunyan in SUB II, grey chips; S. Taylor, Nursing lab, Maya Angelou, Minority students reception; P. Riordan, D. Wilson, J. Burns, R. Herlihy, B & secretaries, Maya Angelou; J. Kostiner, SUB II staff, H. Linedecker; HVAC crews at work, Electric Engineering lab, Zaffke, B. Reed, LeResche
    - 1988, March 4-25, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      Siff, Jenkins, Skog, Juli Jones, Gibb & Carroll, Science & Technology faculty group; Egon Verheyen, Jim Trefil, Paul D'Andrea; Students in library; Computer training class; Susan Campbell, Margaret Mills, June Hull, Shirley Devier, Bedford Thomas, Mary Boyle, Kathy Adcock, William Rorabaugh, Bonnie Hankins, Hope Williams / John Jenkins; Joseph Gittler, Larry Bowen, Arthur Sanders, Mary Blecins, Charlene Calder, Pearl Daniels, Helen Barton, Elva Fones, Barbara Blundell; Abdi Bile in training facility and weight room; Ed Wegman in computer lab; Forensics Tourney, GMU: Leonard Bennett, Alan Stewart, Wake Forest: Lyle Scruggs, Mark Bailey; Anne Winther-Hausen, Margaret Anne Allen, James Bush, Helen Todd, Jennifer Hartt; Hugh Sockett, Robert Ruhling, Barry Beyer, Larry Bowen, Ed Jones, Jeremy Burnham, Robert Gilstrap, Albert Edgemon, Bill Miller; Doug Walker; Barry Render, Biology lab, daffodil distribution; Electron microscope, Cub Scouts visit WGMU; graduate student in lecture and seminar
    - 1988, March 28-April 18, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      Pete Kennedy at Bias studio; Bruce Manchester, Sheryl Friedly, Forensics mock competition; Graduate student teaching, Biology lab; David Kuebrich, Kurt Seiberlich, Diane Turner, Steve Coleman, Amy Thompson, Amanda Even, Ed Henry, Finley lobby and Finley portrait; Saul Bakash, John Paden, Faculty books; Biology class, Forensics mock competition; Jim Laue, Johan Galtung; John C. Wood; Students on campus; King Hall dedication, David King; Graduate Nursing seminar; Ed Wegman; Warren Decker, David Steinberg, Abdi Bile in class; Paula Lewis; Mary Catherine Bateson, Robinson professors' lunch meeting, Kenneth Heller; Edward King, Dave Kapalko, Roger Kammerdeiner, Monica Neighbors, Roberto Marquez, Paul D'Andrea; Michael Ferri, Larry Bowen, Terry Weeks, Darlene Pierce, construction on campus
    - 1988, April 18-May 11, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      Construction on campus (Art Center complex), Arthur Sanders, photo ID system; Elanor Symption, Donald Gallehr, Jim Grey; Admissions luncheon; Joan Shindel; Campus scenes; Mason Scholars; Fleishman, Buffardi, Mason Day, Behrman, Gall, Carr and dog; Cary Kimble and family at V.C.C.A (home); Dick Bausch with Cary Kimble, campus, woods, quad; Bob Fletcher, Michael (Randy) Gabel and Evans Mandes, Thomas Hill and Mary Cabell, Paula Lewis; Ed Heath, Charlene Gross, Kenneth Kelly; David Bailey, Carl Harris, Alan Cheuse, Fenwick Library; Paul D'Andrea, Saul Bakash and Roberto Marquez; James Trefil, Robinson Professors visit to Artificial Intelligence lab; Hemlock Overlook; Thelma Levine teaching, Roberto Marquez teaching; Egon Verheyen teaching, Roger Wilkins teaching; Carlos Feuntes in his office
    - 1988, May 12-June 21, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      Roberto Marquez in his office, Roger Wilkins in office, Shaul Bakash in class; Tom Burns in class; John Paden in class, office scenes, Egon Verheyen in office; ECAC Women's track meet; Job Fair in Patriot Center; Warren Doyle, Wayne Anderson, Pam Tribino; Patriot Center, Art Center construction; Campus scenes; Sculpture on campus; Robert Hazen at Geophysical Lab (D.C.); pipe problem at Hanover (after repairs), campus scenes; student mural in SUB I; car crushed by fallen tree (Patriot Center)
    - 1988, June 27-August 22, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      Jean-Paul Dumont with Peter Black and L. Golumb; Hugh Hello; John C. Woods in office, campus scenes; GMU / Shenandoah College press conference; Ernie Burger, check passing, Juliette Johnson, Shirley Coles; Nicole Liva, Brian Trent, Kevin Mobley, Lamar McCowen; David Swanson, Marjorie Haley, Michale McCullion; Wayne Anderson, Mary Fernald, Ernie Nestor; William A. Hazel; Robert Jones, Alex Ayers (alum); John Wood, Ken Reid (alum), campus scenes; New student orientation; Donna Bafundo, Keith Warner; George Vaughan and Kathleen McGuinness; Ken Bumgarner, John Spaldo, Lori Tiller, Adrienne Hillery, Ken Kelly, Don Rosenblum, John O'Malley, Michael (Randy) Gabel; copy shots of John C. Wood, C.K. WIlliams, Mary Morris, Vassily Aksyonov, Herbert Gold, C. Michael Curtis; soccer
    - 1988, August 24-September 16, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      Richard Wagner, George's Hall Entrepreneurship Center setups (SBA); Randall Edwards, J. Jenkins with new mainframe, L. Brown, Dunn, Flynn; Jerry Jenkins with new IBM academic computing system; Mrs. Johnson with Drewer, Zalokar; New student picnic on quard, President George Johnson; fraternity sign-up tables, classroom and hallway scenes in Robinson; G. Mushrush, L. Irvine, campus; Nursing group, students on the quad; Wilkie Leith, Larry Bostian, Jazz Ensemble rehearsing in Art Center; Clara Lovett, Dave Schaefer, Jack High with NASA study group; K. Gentemann, C. Raphael, J. Trefil, R. Fairley in computer class; Alan Cheuse, Vassily Aksyonov, students, Coleman Raphael; Pete Kennedy with Charlie Byrd at King of France Tavern, Annapolis, Maryland
    - 1988, September 16-October 20, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      Pete Kennedy in Annapolis; B. Beyer, R. Diecchio, D. Dinan, Memorial trees, students; Charles Smith, Humanities II construction, Grotophorst, Hurt and Health, Memorial trees; Patriot's Day, Patriot's village, Field House parking lot; Early identification workshop; Pete Kennedy at home, Janet Reid, Faculty Art Show reception; J. Kvancz, Jeanne and Jim Hendrix, Georgia Panther, campus shots, W. Doyle; H. Morowitz, E. Berger, C. Mitchell, Connie Kirkland; Gala committee tour Humanities II, Finley portrait dedication (includes prints)
      contact sheets, negatives, prints
    - 1988, October 24-November 1, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      UVA vs. GMU soccer; Ernie Nestor; basketball practice; Moscow circus, Governor Baliles; Black Student leadership conference; Faculty Art Show, Academic Computer Center ribbon cutting
    - 1988, November 3-December 6, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      Westphal, Bolstein, D. Vaughn teaching, Cosmo, campus, students; Sue Fitzgerald, "Green Team", J. Walker, Memorial trees; E. Nestor portraits and jogging; Jim Lewis, women's basketball practice; Arts Gala, Finley portrait, Smith charts, Market Process seminar; J. Skog, F. Foldvary, campus, local government forum, J. Warner; M. Behrman, M. Scherrens, "New ways to collage" show, Nancy Schulte; NVCC Annandale campus, campus buildings interiors, check donation, copies; dance concert rehearsal; PAGE students in interviews in lounge
    - 1988, December 8-21, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      Campus snow scenes, Marie Walsh, PAGE student interview; indoor track and field; Army Reserve induction of Lorraine Rudowski; Mason Scholars; "Lid Lifter" women's track meet; Jazz Ensemble rehearsal in Harris, staircase shots in Art Center; Black Box theatre, piano student practicing, modules; Dance setups in Art Center rehearsal room; P. Caretta, dance setups, Humanities, Soviet lunch, students, SUB I, LAWS copy
    - 1989, January 10-February 6, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      D. Walsch, C. Werth, J. Blundell, T. Ward, Mail Room, Smith and Coles; Unidentified contact sheets - faculty and staff, students, campus scenes
    - 1989, February 10-March 1, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      T. Dunn, J. Malinky, M. Moyer with wrestling team, admissions staff; visiting student families, slide duplicatior flash exposure tests; V. Feeg, J. Wood, visiting student families, H. Carter copies; K. Alligood, T Sauer, D. Welpe, E. Hagamon; J. Stampp, J. Palmer, dressing room and Midsummer Night's Dream, crocus; Student job fair in Patriot's Center, student and staff aerobics class (Betsy); generic building shots for Capital Campaign, S. Gould lecture
    - 1989, March 8-24, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      J. Buchanan, L. Cook with E. Partin, needlework award, snow scenes; H. Butler, R. Kerns, M. Mobley, A. Andrews and O. Brand, library scenes; J. Clarke, P. Kropp, Don Rosenblum with S. Gaddy and L. Azad; McDonald's cup gymnastic competition in the Patriot Center; College dance competition, Odadaa! master class; Dan Wagoner and dancers and ballet master classes; College dance competition master classes, Odadaa!; E. Cassara, W. Wehrle, Barbara Mack, A. Sood, J. Stein; Bagyula and Showers, J. Granfield, GWJ and K. Reid, computer art exhibit
    - 1989, March 27-April 7, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      Avruch teaching, chemistry labs, visiting families, students studying; Forche class, International week quad scenes, woman on the wall; Students in science labs; T. Burns seminar, biology lab, students in Thompson computer lab; K. Hoffman teaching, Gala committee tour, woman in computer lab; C. Genrich, P. King, J. Hale, S. Studds, S. Burgess; R. Wilkens journalism class, classroom shots, groups, and individuals; E. Fagenson, D. Lepard, J. Mellinger, sculpture class
    - 1989, April 10-24, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      K. Studd and dance class, G. Mushrush with liquid nitrogen show; D. Bever in firefighter training, M. Andino with bowl; Joe Fisher, Cluster dorm and SUB II scenes, Ruben Vartanyan; Freidley, Metcalf, Rein, Warkentin, Ro, Holman; G. Bruce-Sanford, L. Tiller, K. Kovach, graduate students studying; Richard Fink, M. Crawford, Black Student leadership conference; LAWS group, metro station, Einstein statue, Mason Scholars
    - 1989, May 3-23, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 1)